blogomonster.com 2008-06-09

# BlogoMonster.com offers free blog hosting, blog templates and more!

Last updated: June 17th, 2007

BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. respects and honors the privacy of your personal information. We want you to have a positive experience while you are on or web site. This privacy policy is to protect any information you have given to us. Any personal information given to BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. will be safeguarded and not disclosed to other web site organizations. 

Any personal information such as: name, address, phone numbers, web addresses, pictures, audio files, and other information pertaining to you is strictly on a volunteer basis. This personal information is restricted to only the BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. web site and we will not allow or distribute the information to any other organizations. 

Personal information that is on the BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. site is used for business only. Only the employees of BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. are allowed to carry out legitimate business functions using personal information retrieved from the site. Employees of BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. will respect all personal information. Violation of this conduct will be subject to prosecution to the fullest extent of the law and/or termination.

While BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. is committed to protecting all personal information on the BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. site, we cannot guarantee the safeguard of the personal information. 

BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. will not accept any personal information that is violation of the law. Such information will be forwarded to the appropriate authorities and will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.

BLOGOMONSTER & BLOGO, INC. reserves the right to change the above mentioned statements at anytime. In doing so, we will inform the visitor of any new policies
